It was amazing.
すごかったね
how was it?
どうだった?
It was really good.
めっちゃよかった
lie?
嘘?
You said it hurt a little.
ちょっと痛いって言ってたじゃん
Isn't that?
あれじゃない?
Because this is how I gave it to you.
こうやってあげてたから
Oh, maybe the legs?
あ、足かな?
You wouldn't do something like this.
こんな体勢のことはしないでしょって
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
But did it feel good?
でも気持ちよかった?
He was pushing me.
押しを出てたもんね
at the beginning.
最初の方で
What did you feel the most?
何番目に気持ちよかったの?
Second.
2番目
Second?
2番目?
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
Who is number 1?
1番は誰?
secret.
内緒
I need to take a shower.
ちょっとシャワー浴びないと
I'll help you.
手伝ってあげるね
picture?
え?
I can't get rid of it.
抜けないもんね
I can't get over it.
抜 け ない も ん ね
What, how about a bath?
え、お風呂は?
You have to get dressed, right?
服着ないといけないでしょ
It's a long way to go to the bathroom.
お風呂行くのにも距離あるから
I have to get dressed.
服着ないといけないじゃん
I don't know who's watching.
誰が見てるかわからないし
Press the button.
ボタン押して
You're going to get dressed.
服着るでしょ
Do you go naked to the convenience store?
コンビニ行くのに裸で行く?
It's a bath, right?
お風呂でしょ
Do you go out naked to go to the bathroom?
お風呂行くのに裸で外出る?
It won't come out.
出ないよね
Enter this.
これ入って
I don't know if people are watching.
人が見てるかわからない
Junior high school student Taro always doesn't open his suit.
中学生太郎の常にスーツ開けないでしょ
be?
ある?
Yes, it's done.
はい、できました
Then let's go.
じゃあ 行こう
You don't go to the bathroom naked, do you?
お風呂行くのに裸で行かないでしょ
Do you go to battle or spa naked?
戦闘とかスパとか裸で行く?
Don't go.
行かないでね
Yes, let's go then.
はい、じゃあ行きましょう
Yes, I'm off to take a bath.
はい、じゃあお風呂来ました
Yes, yes, yes.
はい、はい、はい
What's missing?
何 がないの?
I don't know who's watching.
誰が見てるかわからない
Take this.
これ 持って
Shall I wash it?
洗ってあげようか
Bring something beautiful.
綺麗なものを持って
beautiful
綺麗
What?
な の?
Bring something beautiful.
綺麗なものを持って
It's looking beautiful.
綺麗になってる
綺麗になってるね
A little bit of this or that.
ちょっとこれ、あれか
I can't do my work because I'm too lazy.
ごたくせーから仕事洗えないから
You better look up.
ちゃんと顔上げたほうがいいよ
You can eat your hair.
髪が食べれちゃうからね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Older child, you haven't had him washed normally.
長い子、普通に洗ってもらってないでしょ
Also, I have to wash my ex-boyfriend.
あとね、元ごんさんとか洗わないと
Gengon
元ごん
I have to wash it.
さん とか洗わないと
So I'm sorry for this situation.
じゃあこの状態で ごめんなさい
Did it become beautiful?
綺麗になったの?
TRUE?
本当?
What about hair?
毛毛とかも?
Does it have a lot of mancon?
マンコンいっぱい付いてるの?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Is it okay then?
じゃあ大丈夫かな?
Did you wash it properly?
ちゃんと洗った?
suit?
スーツ?
Oh, I'm just washing it.
あれ、洗ってるだけだよ
Why, are you putting this out with a slightly naughty feel?
なんと、ちょっとエブい感じでこれ出すの?
Does that mean it's not enough?
足んないってこと?
Isn't that adult sexy enough?
あんなの大人セクシーってまだ足んない?
That's amazing.
すごいね
I was exposed.
よくばれたんだ
I need to wash it thoroughly.
きれいに洗っとかないとね
That's amazing.
すごい ね
The feeling of the air.
空気の感じが
It turns white when air enters it.
空気が入ると 白くなるね
interesting.
面白い
Did it stick?
張り付いた?
It's not good at all.
なん も良くないね
How many?
何本?
It's beautiful now.
綺麗になったね
It's really heavy.
めちゃめちゃ重たい
heavy?
重たい?
Isn't it heavy?
重たいでしょ?
I need to get one soon.
1個ぐらい早く取らなきゃ
What, in the end?
え、結局?
I washed it with my suit.
スーツと一緒に洗ったから
yes.
はい
Get in
入れ
While.
な がら
Leave it like this.
このまま
Put it in.
入れて
Put it in again.
また入れて
Do you want to stay here?
ここはたまっておき?
Oh, uh, there's a lot of accumulation here.
あ、あの、 ここはたまって
Accumulate?
たまって?
Is this place tamarou?
ここはたまろう?
No, this is no good.
いや、こっちはダメだよ
So, should I put it here?
あって、ここにかける?
What?
あって?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
You can wash it well like this, right?
このままよく洗えるでしょ?
When you have someone wash your clothes, you can't do it unless you take turns, right?
洗ってもらうときはやっぱり 交代しないと洗えないでしょ?
You better give your buddy a good wash, right?
仲間にしっかり洗い流したほうがいいでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Because I liked it.
好 きだったからね
It's better to have proper skin.
ちゃんと肌ついたほうがいいからね
Get it right.
ちゃん とね
why?
なんで?
picture?
え?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Open your legs.
足開いて
I found something that wasn't hot water.
お湯じゃないやつ出たね
The hot water came out.
お湯入ってたのが出た
Oh, is that so?
あ、そういうこと?
Wash it thoroughly if you like.
よかったらきれいに洗ってね
Okay.
いいよ
Yes, it's clean now.
はい、きれいになりました
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
More than that, a suit.
それよりね、 スーツがね
It's blocked.
塞いでるね
No, no, no.
違う違う違う
That's not true.
そうじゃないのよ
A suit for everyday life.
着る生活のためのスーツがさ
Will you wear this?
これ着る?
Messed up.
めちゃめちゃ
If I wear it now, I'll catch a cold.
今着たら風邪ひいてる
What should we do?
どうしましょう?
What should I do?
どうすればいい?